In this section of the course, we'll take a quick tour of the CodeLite IDE interface.
It's important to feel comfortable with the environment
that we're using to create our c++ programs.
So I'll walk you through the major functionality of the CodeLite IDE,
so you can get up and running quickly.
Then we'll write our first c++ program.
It'll be a pretty simple program that simply asks the user for their favorite number
and then displays it on the console.
We'll use this program to look at the build options provided by CodeLite,
and I'll show you how they work and what they do.
Finally, we'll introduce some problems into our program
so that you can see some of the typical errors
and warnings that you'll probably encounter as you write c++ programs
and understand them and know how to fix them.
That's it. This section short and simple, but very, very important
since it lays the foundation for writing,
building and running c++ programs in the CodeLite IDE.
Let's get started.